{
    "subject": "resource/Goopy_Gyne_Bagha_Byne",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/Satyajit_Ray",
    "human_readable": "Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne was written by Satyajit Ray.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9649107456207275,
            "question": "Who wrote the story Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9503299593925476,
            "question": "Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne is a story by which author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9379268884658813,
            "question": "What is the name of the author who wrote Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8004082441329956,
            "question": "Is Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne a popular story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6677985787391663,
            "question": "Can you name a book written by Satyajit Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5577092170715332,
            "question": "What kind of stories did Satyajit Ray write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4996914267539978,
            "question": "Is Satyajit Ray known for writing stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49303939938545227,
            "question": "What famous literary work was created by Satyajit Ray?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41256481409072876,
            "question": "Besides writing stories, what else is Satyajit Ray known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27171412110328674,
            "question": "What are some of Satyajit Ray's other works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne was written by Satyajit Ray.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4104_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides writing stories, what else is Satyajit Ray known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4104_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What famous literary work was created by Satyajit Ray?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4104_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Satyajit Ray known for writing stories?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4104_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4104_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nAll the documents mention that Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne is a film directed, written and scored by Satyajit Ray. Therefore, this information supports the triple that Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne was written by Satyajit Ray."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Goopy Gyne Bagha Byne (1968) was written, scored and directed by Satyajit Ray,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}